<articles>
    <article id="0" title="What is a goat?" level="1" lvlIncrease="1">
        A goat is a mammal with all the hooves and none of the decency. From this can be all derived. In a fact, it is such a universal claim,
        that to imagine a world without goats is a bleak and pitiful existence without ANY redeeming qualities. To the trainee goatist, the seemingly
        insurmountable odds of overcoming any irrational fear of upgoating can be overcome by discipline and precision of mind, which can be
        sharpened by defining these creatures of utmost importance. Let's see it in practise:

        1. A goat is everything, which is, by nature not not a goat.

        2. A goat is an animal, on which the number of limbs attached by the forces of nature never exceeds that of a donkey or a horse, and while this number
        is inferior to that of cockroaches, it never entails any kind of species-wise inferiority. The reason behind that lies in a factor that
        predisposes goat limbs to be multi-faceted constructions of compound appendages due to them having thick fur, in which each piece of hair can be considered
        a separate leg by invertebrate standards. In a sense, it can be said, that goats have limbs in the number of hundred-thousands. Can donkey-hair or horse-hair
        considered as well to be an array of legs? No, as it's quite obvious that equines and their relatives cannot jump on fences, rooftops or other elevated platforms,
        on the other hand, goats can. This can be only explained by the latter having a high number of legs (which provides great extra strength), and the former don't.
        In other words, to the caprine, fur is legs, to other hoofed kindred, fur is just ... fur. A goat is, therefore, very good.

    </article>
    <article id="1" title="Goat breeding" level="1" lvlIncrease="1">
        Try to raise your number of goats. Hint: Add goats to make more goats. If you have enough goats, you don't have enough goats. Ideal goat population approaches
        infinity. Ideal human population doesn't. Conclusion: don't have children, have goats instead and breed them. Or even better, find yourself a team of decently
        drunken surgeons, so that by the miracle of scalpels and blood and saws and blood and drills and blood and hammers and blood and sutures and blood and just a hint of
        neo-Freudean charlatanry, you can become a goat yourself. Find friends; become goats together; make doctors exhausted, overworked and devilishly rich. You poor
        bastard, deep inside you know, you can never become one of these fine creatures. So you come up with stupid ideas, like this? Shame!
    </article>
    <article id="2" title="Teaching your goats moral nihilism" level="3" lvlIncrease="1">
        You can teach your goats the base values of moral nihilism like this: public class MyGoat() extends Goat { private Boolean goodOrBad = null;}
    </article>
    <article id="3" title="Goat refactoring 101" level="4" lvlIncrease="1">
        Goats are to be refactored constantly for the greater good of goatkind. It is good.
    </article>
    <article id="4" title="Putting your goat before your needs" level="5" lvlIncrease="1">
        Die for your goat. No exception.
    </article>
    <article id="5" title="Dealing with the public: It is a calling, not an obsession!"  level="6" lvlIncrease="1">
        So far, you have learned valuable lessons stemming from the basic proposition: Goats are great. However, public support for
        the cause may diminish each time you talk about goats, refer to goat food or mimic the calls of goats. There is a reason for that:
        For others, goats are not that great. What to do? It's easy: have ample time to refer to your oppositions' mothers. This will undermine
        their statements and make their very rhetoric collapse by its own weight.
    </article>
</articles>
